The phase two A study in atopic dermatitis is now recruiting.
The vitiligo study,
is set to begin.
Obviously, if we can show meaningful improvements over the standard of care in atopic dermatitis, or can obviously become a standard of care in vitiligo, these would be very large indications.
I wouldn't be in a position to give you precise numbers, but obviously very large market opportunities.
And we are actively looking at moving that IL-15 across multiple other immunology indications over time.
So I think as we,
as we progress,
we'll,
we'll, of course,
you know, keep,
you know, keep you posted.
And maybe I'll also note in atopic dermatitis,
we also have the GHC program,
which also IL-13, IL-18, which we're also,
you know, on track.
Thank you.
As a reminder,
if you would like to ask a question,
please press star one and one on your telephone and wait for your name to be announced.
Please limit yourself to one question and return to the queue for any follow up.
Thank you.
We'll now take the next question.
And the question comes from the line of Matthew Weston from UBS.
Please go ahead.
Thanks, Vass.
It's a quick follow up about my first question about RAPSEDO and and XUS.
And I was intrigued by your comment around you coming in for US approval before MFN.
Just thinking about the CNS indication,
which I think you've said previously is going to have a separate brand name,
but obviously,
the same active ingredient at a different dose. Does that mean it would also be excluded from
MFN considerations because of the original approval, or that's something that we'd have
to think of in MS? Yeah, so our current assumption, Matthew, it's a very good question. Our current
assumption, working assumption, is that this is based on the chemical compound in question. So
all, because remibrutinib has an approval that even with different brand names that all of the
subsequent remibrutinib indications would be susceptible to the Medicaid element of the MFN
story, but not the overall MFN across all segments of U.S. reimbursement environment.
I would say that is our current working assumption, and if that changes, we'll let you
know. But our current expectation is that would be how remibrutinib would be treated, as would be